Time. All right, Klingons, pencils down.
(Leonard:)Okay, I have pokh.
ALL:
Got it.
[SPEAKING IN KLINGON]
ALL:
Yep.
(All:)Got it.
- I have chorrr.
ALL: Got it.
ALL: Yeah.
- And kreplach.
- Hold on a second, kreplach?
- Yeah.
(Raj:)That isn't Klingon.
It's Yiddish for meat-filled dumpling.
(Howard:)Well, as it turns out,
it's also a Klingon word.
(Leonard:)Really? Define it.
Kreplach, a hearty Klingon dumpling.
(Raj:)Judge's ruling?
[SPEAKS IN KLINGON]
(Penny(entering):)Hey, guys. I need to use your TV.
- What's wrong with your TV?
- I don't know. Just died. I'm getting static.
(Howard:)Did you pay your cable bill?
Ugh. You sound
just like the cable company.
(Penny:)All right, so shh. Tyra Banks is about to
kick someone off America's Next Top Model.